{
    "id": "f33ccf0427444cf0b5b1dcab978eba96",
    "title": "Articles Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He told me ……………………… interesting story yesterday.",
            "description": "Use a/an to mean one. A singular countable noun requires an article.",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the",
                "No article"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He has ………………….. keen eye for detail.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the",
                "No article"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………. life is complicated.",
            "description": "We do not normally use an article with uncountable nouns when we are talking about things in general. ",
            "answers": [
                "A",
                "The",
                "No article"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………… minister ordered ………………………. official inquiry into ……………………… incident.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "The, an, an",
                "A, the, the",
                "The, an, the"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He has no interest in …………………….. politics.",
            "description": "We do not normally use articles with the names of subjects. ",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the",
                "No article"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She learned ………………………… philosophy at university.",
            "description": "We do not normally use articles with the names of subjects. ",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the",
                "No article"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Raju is …………………….. accomplished cook. ………………………. dinner he gave us yesterday was delicious.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "an, The",
                "the, The",
                "an, A"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I reserved ……………………. table for three.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the",
                "No article"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "................................ suspect was taken into …………………………. custody.",
            "description": "Suspect is a singular countable noun we have to use an article with singular countable nouns there is no article in the expression take into custody.",
            "answers": [
                "No articles are required",
                "The, no article",
                "No article, the"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. person who died in ……………………… riot was ……………………. social activist.",
            "description": "We use the to identify someone. A/an is an indefinite article and it does not mention who we are talking about.",
            "answers": [
                "The, the, a",
                "A, a, the",
                "The, the, the",
                "A, a, a"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………….. tea is very strong. Please pour some more milk into it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "A",
                "The",
                "No article"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "What ……………………… pity that you failed ……………………….. test.",
            "description": "The correct expression is what a pity.",
            "answers": [
                "a, the",
                "the, the",
                "No articles"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}